(Sheldon:)I'm not unsympathetic to your plight.
(Sheldon:)My father used to say
that a woman is like...
(Sheldon:)...an egg salad sandwich
on a warm Texas day.
(Leonard (jumping and knocking over the Jenga):)What?
(Sheldon:)Full of eggs and only appealing
for a short time.
(Alex:)This conversation
is making me uncomfortable.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, you and me both, sister.
(Sheldon:)Please understand, I don't hold you
responsible for your behavior.
(Sheldon:)From an evolutionary standpoint,
you're a slave to your desire to reproduce.
(Sheldon:)But during the work day...
(Sheldon:)...when you feel possessed
by amorous intent, may I suggest...
(Sheldon:)...you suppress it by leafing through
this illustrated book...
(Sheldon:)...of sexually transmitted diseases.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes. Check out this oozy doozy.
(Alex:)I have to go.
(Sheldon:)So does this fellow, but he
can't without it burning like hot soup.